A Guide to the Recordings of the Virginia House of Delegates Sessions, 1981-2013
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Recordings, 1981-2012., Extent: 23.55 cu. ft. (79 boxes). (Box 1-78)
  - 1991 (DVD)., .81 cu. ft. (3 boxes) (Box 37 - 39)
    - 1991 Jan 29. (Box 37)
    - 1991 Jan 30. (Box 37)
    - 1991 Feb 1. (Box 37)
    - 1991 Feb 1, 2. (Box 37)
    - 1991 Feb 2. (Box 37)
    - 1991 Feb 2, 3. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 3 (2 discs). (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 3, 4. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 4 (4 disks). (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 4, 5, 6. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 6, 7. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 7. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 7, 8. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 11-12. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 13. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 14. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 14, 15. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 15, 18. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 19. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 19, 20. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 20. (Box 38)
    - 1991 Feb 20, 21. (Box 39)
    - 1991 Feb 21 (3 discs). (Box 39)
    - 1991 Feb 22. (Box 39)
    - 1991 Feb 22, 23. (Box 39)
    - 1991 Feb 23 (2 discs). (Box 39)
    - 1991 Apr 1-2, 3. (Box 39)
    - 1991 Apr 3. (Box 39)
    - 1991 Apr 3, 4, 5. (Box 39)
    - 1991 Apr 5. (Box 39)
    - 1991 Apr 5, 6. (Box 39)
    - 1991 Apr 6, 9. (Box 39)
    - 1991 Apr 30. (Box 39)
    - 1991 May 21; July 1, 19. (Box 39)
    - 1991 Nov 18, 19, 20. (Box 39)
    - 1991 Nov 20 (2 discs). (Box 39)
    - 1991 Dec 9. (Box 39)
  - 1992 (DVD)., 1 cu. ft. (4 boxes) (Box 40 - 43)
    - 1992 Jan 8 (2 discs). (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 9-10, 13-15. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 16-17. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 20. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 21-22. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 23. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 24. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 27 (2 discs). (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 28. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 29. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 29, 30. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 30, 31. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Jan 31. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Feb 3. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Feb 4. (Box 40)
    - 1992 Feb 5 (2 discs). (Box 40)
    - 1992 Feb 6 (2 discs). (Box 40, 41)
    - 1992 Feb 7 (2 discs). (Box 41)
    - 1992 Feb 8 (2 discs). (Box 41)
    - 1992 Feb 9 (2 discs). (Box 41)
    - 1992 Feb 10 (5 discs). (Box 41)
    - 1992 Feb 11 (2 discs). (Box 41)
    - 1992 Feb 12, 13. (Box 41)
    - 1992 Feb 13, 14. (Box 41)
    - 1992 Feb 14 (2 discs). (Box 41)
    - 1992 Feb 17. (Box 42)
    - 1992 Feb 18. (Box 42)
    - 1992 Feb 19. (Box 42)
    - 1992 Feb 20 (5 discs). (Box 42)
    - 1992 Feb 21 (2 discs). (Box 42)
    - 1992 Feb 24 (2 discs). (Box 42)
    - 1992 Feb 25. (Box 42)
    - 1992 Feb 26 (2 discs). (Box 42)
    - 1992 Feb 27. (Box 42)
    - 1992 Feb 27, 28. (Box 42)
    - 1992 Feb 28 (2 discs). (Box 42)
    - 1992 Mar 2 (2 discs). (Box 42, 43)
    - 1992 Mar 3, 4. (Box 43)
    - 1992 Mar 4. (Box 43)
    - 1992 Mar 5 (5 discs). (Box 43)
    - 1992 Mar 6. (Box 43)
    - 1992 Mar 6, 7. (Box 43)
    - 1992 Mar 7 (3 discs). (Box 43)
    - 1992 Apr 15 (4 discs). (Box 43)
    - 1992 May 27 (2 discs). (Box 43)
  - 1993 (DVD)., 1 cu. ft. (4 boxes) (Box 44 - 47)
    - 1993 Jan 13, 14. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Jan 15, 18, 19, 20. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Jan 20, 21, 22, 25. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Jan 25, 26. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Jan 26. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Jan 26, 27. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Jan 27, 28. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Jan 29. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Jan 29; Feb 1. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Feb 2. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Feb 3. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Feb 3, 4. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Feb 4, 5. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Feb 5 (2 discs). (Box 44)
    - 1993 Feb 6 (2 discs). (Box 44)
    - 1993 Feb 6, 7. (Box 44)
    - 1993 Feb 7 (2 discs). (Box 44, 45)
    - 1993 Feb 7, 8. (Box 45)
    - 1993 Feb 8 (5 discs). (Box 45)
    - 1993 Feb 8, 9. (Box 45)
    - 1993 Feb 9 (4 discs). (Box 45)
    - 1993 Feb 9, 10, 11. (Box 45)
    - 1993 Feb 11, 12. (Box 45)
    - 1993 Feb 12, 15, 16. (Box 45)
    - 1993 Feb 16, 17. (Box 45)
    - 1993 Feb 19. (Box 45)
    - 1993 Feb 19, 22. (Box 45)
    - 1993 Feb 22. (Box 46)
    - 1993 Feb 22, 23. (Box 46)
    - 1993 Feb 23 (4 discs). (Box 46)
    - 1993 Feb 24 (3 discs). (Box 46)
    - 1993 Feb 24, 25. (Box 46)
    - 1993 Feb 25 (3 discs). (Box 46)
    - 1993 Feb 26. (Box 46)
    - 1993 Feb 26, 27. (Box 46)
    - 1993 Feb 27 (4 discs). (Box 46)
    - 1993 Feb 22. (Box 46)
    - 1993 Apr 7 (5 discs). (Box 47)
    - 1993 May 19. (Box 47)
  - 1994 (DVD)., 1.3 cu. ft. (5 boxes) (Box 47 - 52)
    - 1994 Jan 12. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Jan 12, 13-14. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Jan 15. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Jan 15, 17. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Jan 17, 18-20. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Jan 21, 24, 25. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Jan 26. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Jan 26, 27, 28. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Jan 28, 31. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Feb 1. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Feb 2, 3. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Feb 3. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Feb 3, 4. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Feb 4, 7. (Box 47)
    - 1994 Feb 7, 8. (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 8. (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 8, 9. (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 9. (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 10 (2 discs). (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 10, 11. (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 11 (3 discs). (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 11, 12. (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 12. (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 13 (2 discs). (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 13, 14. (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 14 (3 discs). (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 14, 15. (Box 48)
    - 1994 Feb 15 (7 discs). (Box 49)
    - 1994 Feb 15, 16, 17. (Box 49)
    - 1994 Feb 17. (Box 49)
    - 1994 Feb 18, 21. (Box 49)
    - 1994 Feb 22, 23. (Box 49)
    - 1994 Feb 23, 24. (Box 49)
    - 1994 Feb 24 (3 discs). (Box 49)
    - 1994 Feb 24, 25. (Box 49)
    - 1994 Feb 25 (2 discs). (Box 49)
    - 1994 Feb 28 (2 discs). (Box 49)
    - 1994 Feb 28; Mar 1. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 1. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 1, 2. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 2. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 2, 3. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 3. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 3, 4. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 4. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 7. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 7, 8. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 8. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 8, 9. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 9 (3 discs). (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 9, 10. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 10 (3 discs). (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 10, 11. (Box 50)
    - 1994 Mar 11 (2 discs). (Box 51)
    - 1994 Mar 11, 12. (Box 51)
    - 1994 Mar 12 (2 discs). (Box 51)
    - 1994 Apr 20 (4 discs). (Box 51)
    - 1994 May 11. (Box 51)
    - 1994 July 6, 7. (Box 51)
    - 1994 July 7. (Box 51)
    - 1994 July 7, 8. (Box 51)
    - 1994 July 8. (Box 51)
    - 1994 Sept 19 (2 discs). (Box 51)
    - 1994 Sept 19, 20. (Box 51)
    - 1994 Sept 27-28, 29 (2 discs). (Box 51)
    - 1994 Sept 29 (2 discs). (Box 51, 52)
    - 1994 Sept 30. (Box 52)
  - 1995 (DVD)., .8 cu. ft. (3 boxes) (Box 52 - 55)
    - 1995 Jan 11 (2 discs). (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 12. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 13. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 16-17. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 18. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 19. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 20. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 23. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 24. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 25. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 26 (2 discs). (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 27. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 30. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 31. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Jan 31; Feb 1. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Feb 1. (Box 52)
    - 1995 Feb 2. (Box 53)
    - 1995 Feb 2, 3. (Box 53)
    - 1995 Feb 3 (2 discs). (Box 53)
    - 1995 Feb 4 (2 discs). (Box 53)
    - 1995 Feb 5 (2 discs). (Box 53)
    - 1995 Feb 6 (5 discs). (Box 53)
    - 1995 Feb 7 (5 discs). (Box 53)
    - 1995 Feb 8. (Box 53)
    - 1995 Feb 9 (3 discs). (Box 53, 54)
    - 1995 Feb 10 (2 discs). (Box 54)
    - 1995 Feb 13. (Box 54)
    - 1995 Feb 14 (2 discs). (Box 54)
    - 1995 Feb 15 (2 discs). (Box 54)
    - 1995 Feb 16 (2 discs). (Box 54)
    - 1995 Feb 17 (2 discs). (Box 54)
    - 1995 Feb 20 (2 discs). (Box 54)
    - 1995 Feb 21 (2 discs). (Box 54)
    - 1995 Feb 22 (4 discs). (Box 54)
    - 1995 Feb 23 (5 discs). (Box 55)
    - 1995 Feb 24 (2 discs). (Box 55)
    - 1995 Feb 25 (2 discs). (Box 55)
    - 1995 Apr 5 (3 discs). (Box 55)
    - 1995 Apr 6 (5 discs). (Box 55)
  - 1996 (VHS)., .54 cu. ft. (2 boxes) (Box 56-57)
    - 1996 Jan 10-12, 15-19. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Jan 22-26. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Jan 29-31. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Feb 1, 2, 5. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Feb 5, 6, 7. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Feb 8, 9. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Feb 10, 12. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Feb 12. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Feb 12, 15. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Feb 13. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Feb 15, 16, 19-22. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Feb 22, 23. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Feb 23, 26, 26. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Feb 28, 29; Mar 1, 4. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Mar 2. (Box 56)
    - 1996 Mar 3. (Box 57)
    - 1996 Mar 4, 5. (Box 57)
    - 1996 Mar 6. (Box 57)
    - 1996 Mar 7, 8. (Box 57)
    - 1996 Mar 9, 10, 11. (Box 57)
    - 1996 Apr 17. (Box 57)
    - 1996. (Box 57)
  - 1997 (VHS)., .96 cu. ft. (3 boxes) (Box 57-59)
    - 1997 Jan 8 (2 tapes). (Box 57)
    - 1997 Jan 13. (Box 57)
    - 1997 Jan 14-21. (Box 57)
    - 1997 Jan 22, 23, 24. (Box 57)
    - 1997 Jan 27. (Box 57)
    - 1997 Jan 27, 28, 29. (Box 57)
    - 1997 Jan 29. (Box 57)
    - 1997 Jan 29, 30, 31. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Jan 31; Feb 1. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 1. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 2, 3. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 3. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 4. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 4, 5, 6. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 7, 10. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 11, 12, 13. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 14, 17. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 18, 19. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 19, 20. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 20, 21. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 21, 22. (Box 58)
    - 1997 Feb 22 (3 tapes). (Box 58, 59)
    - 1997 Apr 2 (2 tapes). (Box 59)
    - 1997. (Box 59)
  - 1998 (DVD and VHS)., .96 cu. ft. (3 boxes) (Box 59-61)
    - 1998 Jan 14 (3 discs). (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 15. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 16. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 17. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 19 (2 discs). (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 20. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 21. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 22. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 23. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 26. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 27. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 28. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 29. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Jan 30 (4 discs). (Box 60)
    - 1998 Feb 2. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Feb 3. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Feb 4 (3 discs). (Box 60)
    - 1998 Feb 5 (3 discs). (Box 60)
    - 1998 Feb 6. (Box 60)
    - 1998 Feb 9 (2 discs). (Box 60)
    - 1998 Feb 6-9, 10. (Box 59)
    - 1998 Feb 10-13. (Box 59)
    - 1998 Feb 14. (Box 59)
    - 1998 Feb 14, 15, 16. (Box 59)
    - 1998 Feb 16, 17. (Box 59)
    - 1998 Feb 17. (Box 59)
    - 1998 Feb 18, 19. (Box 59)
    - 1998 Feb 23, 24. (Box 59)
    - 1998 Feb 25, 26. (Box 59)
    - 1998 Feb 26, 27; Mar 2, 3. (Box 59)
    - 1998 Mar 3, 4. (Box 61)
    - 1998 Mar 5, 6, 9. (Box 61)
    - 1998 Mar 9, 10, 11. (Box 61)
    - 1998 Mar 12 (2 tapes). (Box 61)
    - 1998 Mar 13, 14. (Box 61)
    - 1998 Mar 14, 15. (Box 61)
    - 1998 Mar 16, 17. (Box 61)
    - 1998 Apr 22. (Box 61)
    - 1998 Apr 23. (Box 61)
    - 1998 Apr 24. (Box 61)
  - 1999 (VHS)., .64 cu. ft. (2 boxes) (Box 61 - 62)
    - 1999 Jan 13-14, 18-19. (Box 61)
    - 1999 Jan 19, 20, 21. (Box 61)
    - 1999 Jan 21, 22, 25. (Box 61)
    - 1999 Jan 25, 26, 27. (Box 61)
    - 1999 Jan 27, 28, 29; Feb 1. (Box 61)
    - 1999 Feb 5, 6. (Box 62)
    - 1999 Feb 7, 8. (Box 62)
    - 1999 Feb 8, 9. (Box 62)
    - 1999 Feb 9, 10. (Box 62)
    - 1999 Feb 10, 11. (Box 62)
    - 1999 Feb 12, 15-17. (Box 62)
    - 1999 Feb 18, 19. (Box 62)
    - 1999 Feb 22. (Box 62)
    - 1999 Feb 22, 23. (Box 62)
    - 1999 Feb 23, 24. (Box 62)
    - 1999 Feb 24. (Box 62)
    - 1999 Apr 7. (Box 62)
  - 2000 (VHS)., .64 cu. ft. (2 boxes) (Box 62 - 63)
    - 2000 Jan 24-28. (Box 62)
    - 2000 Jan 31; Feb 1, 2. (Box 62)
    - 2000 Feb 3, 4. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 7, 8. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 8, 9. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 9, 10. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 10, 11, 12. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 12-14. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 14. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 14, 15. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 15-17. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 17, 18, 21. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 21, 22, 23. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 24. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 24, 25, 28. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 29; Mar 1. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Mar 1, 2. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Mar 2, 3. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 3, 4. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 6, 7. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 7, 8. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 8, 9. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 9, 10. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Feb 10. (Box 63)
    - 2000 Apr 19 (2 tapes). (Box 63)
  - 2001 (VHS)., .64 cu. ft. (2 boxes) (Box 64 - 65)
    - 2001 Jan 18-20. (Box 64)
    - 2001 Jan 24-26. (Box 64)
    - 2001 Jan 26, 29. (Box 64)
    - 2001 Jan 30, 31. (Box 64)
    - 2001 Jan 31. (Box 64)
    - 2001 Feb 2, 3. (Box 64)
    - 2001 Feb 4, 5. (Box 64)
    - 2001 Feb 5. (Box 64)
    - 2001 Feb 6. (Box 64)
    - 2001 Feb 6, 7. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Feb 8. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Feb 8, 9, 12, 14. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Feb 14, 15. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Feb 15, 16, 18. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Feb 19, 20. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Feb 20, 21. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Feb 21, 22. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Feb 23. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Feb 24. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Apr 4, 5. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Apr 10, 11. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Apr 17, 18. (Box 65)
    - 2001 Apr 26; May 3, 4, 7, 8. (Box 65)
    - 2001 May 8, 9. (Box 65)
  - 2002 (VHS)., 1.35 cu. ft. (5 boxes) (Box 66-71)
    - 2002 Jan 9 (5 tapes). (Box 66)
    - 2002 Jan 10. (Box 66)
    - 2002 Jan 11. (Box 66)
    - 2002 Jan 12. (Box 66)
    - 2002 Jan 14 (2 tapes). (Box 66)
    - 2002 Jan 15. (Box 66)
    - 2002 Jan 16. (Box 66)
    - 2002 Jan 17. (Box 66)
    - 2002 Jan 18. (Box 66)
    - 2002 Jan 21. (Box 66)
  - 2003 (DVD)., .2 cu. ft. (1 box) (Box 72)
  - 2004 (DVD)., .34 cu ft (2 boxes) (Box 72-73)
    - 2004 Mar 1. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 2. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 3. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 4. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 5. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 8. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 9. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 10. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 11. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 12. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 13. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 15. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 16. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 17. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 18. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 19. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 20. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 21. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 27. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Mar 30. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Apr 6. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Apr 7. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Apr 12. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Apr 13. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Apr 20. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Apr 21. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Apr 23. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Apr 27. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Apr 30. (Box 73)
    - 2004 May 6. (Box 73)
    - 2004 May 7. (Box 73)
    - 2004 June 16. (Box 73)
    - 2004 July 13. (Box 73)
    - 2004 Aug 18. (Box 73)
  - 2005 (DVD)., .34 cu. ft. (2 boxes) (Box 73-74)
    - 2005 Jan 12. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 13. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 14. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 17. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 18. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 19. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 20. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 21. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 24. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 25. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 26. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 27. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 28. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Jan 31. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 1. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 2. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 3. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 4. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 5. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 7. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 8. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 9. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 10. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 11. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 14. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 15. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 16. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 17. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 18. (Box 73)
    - 2005 Feb 21. (Box 74)
    - 2005 Feb 22. (Box 74)
    - 2005 Feb 23. (Box 74)
    - 2005 Feb 24. (Box 74)
    - 2005 Feb 25. (Box 74)
    - 2005 Feb 26. (Box 74)
    - 2005 Feb 27. (Box 74)
    - 2005 Apr 6. (Box 74)
  - 2006 (DVD)., .34 cu. ft. (2 boxes) (Box 74-75)
    - 2006 Jan 11. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 12. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 13. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 14. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 16. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 17. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 18. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 19. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 20. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 23. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 24. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 25. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 26. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 27. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 30. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Jan 31. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 1. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 2. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 3. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 6. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 7. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 8. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 9. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 10. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 11. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 13. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 14. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 15. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 16. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 17. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 20. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 21. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 22. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 23. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 24. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 27. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Feb 28. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Mar 1. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Mar 2. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Mar 3. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Mar 6. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Mar 7. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Mar 8. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Mar 9. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Mar 10. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Mar 11. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Mar 27. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Mar 30. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Apr 3. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Apr 10. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Apr 11. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Apr 12. (Box 74)
    - 2006 Apr 19. (Box 75)
    - 2006 Apr 26. (Box 75)
    - 2006 Apr 27. (Box 75)
    - 2006 May 3. (Box 75)
    - 2006 May 10. (Box 75)
    - 2006 May 12. (Box 75)
    - 2006 May 18. (Box 75)
    - 2006 May 23. (Box 75)
    - 2006 May 25. (Box 75)
    - 2006 May 30. (Box 75)
    - 2006 June 6. (Box 75)
    - 2006 June 13. (Box 75)
    - 2006 June 16. (Box 75)
    - 2006 June 20. (Box 75)
    - 2006 June 28. (Box 75)
    - 2006 July 24. (Box 75)
    - 2006 Aug 8. (Box 75)
    - 2006 Aug 28. (Box 75)
    - 2006 Sept 27. (Box 75)
    - 2006 Nov 8. (Box 75)
  - 2007-2011 (DVD)., 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes) (Box 76-77)
    - 2007-2009. (Box 76)
    - 2010-2011. (Box 77)
  - 2012 (DVD)., 1 cu. ft. (1 box, 61 dvds) (Box 78)
  - 2013 (DVD)., 1 cu. ft. (1 box, 46 dvds) (Box 79)